http://www.metpipe.com/privacy

Effective on December 27, 2011
This privacy statement describes how Metropolitan Pipe collects and uses the personal information you provide on our Web site: www.metpipe.com. It also describes the choices available to you regarding our use of your personal information and how you can access and update this information. If you have questions or concerns regarding this policy, please contact us at ecomm@metpipe.com.
Collection and Use of Personal Information
We collect the following personal information from you:
Contact Information such as name, email address, mailing address, phone number
Billing Information such as credit card number, and billing address
Unique Identifiers such as user name, account number, password
Preferences Information such as product wish lists, order history, marketing preferences
As is true of most Web sites, we automatically gather information about your computer such as your IP address, browser type, referring/exit pages, and operating system. We use this information to:
Fulfill your order
Send you an order confirmation
Assess the needs of your business to determine suitable products
Send you requested product or service information
Send product updates or warranty information
Respond to customer service requests
Administer your account
Send you a newsletter
Send you marketing communications
Administer contests and sweepstakes you entered, and notify you if you won
Respond to your questions and concerns
Improve our Web site and marketing efforts
Conduct research and analysis
Display content based upon your interests
Choice/Opt-Out
You may choose to stop receiving our newsletter or marketing emails by following the unsubscribe instructions included in these emails or you can contact us at ecomm@metpipe.com.
We enable you to create a profile, and share information such as messages, photos, and videos with others. Please note that we cannot control the actions of others with whom you may choose to share your pages and information.
Information Obtained from Third Parties
We obtain address information about you from third party sources, such as the US Postal Service, to verify your address so we can properly ship your order to you and to prevent fraud.
If you provide us personal information about others, or if others give us your information, we will only use that information for the specific reason for which it was provided to us.
Information Sharing
We will share your personal information with third parties only in the ways that are described in this privacy statement. We do not sell your personal information to third parties.
We may also disclose your personal information as required by law such as to comply with a subpoena or similar legal process when we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud, or respond to a government request. If Metropolitan Pipe is involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, you will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our Web site of any change in ownership or uses of your personal information, as well as any choices you may have regarding your personal information, to any other third party with your prior consent to do so.
Google Checkout
If you choose to use Google Checkout to finalize and pay for your order, you will provide your credit card number directly to Google Checkout. Google’s privacy policy will apply to the information you provide on the Google Checkout Web site.
PayPal
If you choose to use PayPal to finalize and pay for your order, you will provide your credit card number, directly to PayPal. PayPal’s privacy policy will apply to the information you provide on the PayPal Web site.
Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies
We may use cookies, for example, to keep track of your preferences and profile information. Cookies are also used to collect general usage and volume statistical information that does not include personal information.
Web beacons
Our Web pages contain electronic images known as Web beacons (sometimes called single-pixel gifs) and are used along with cookies to compile aggregated statistics to analyze how our site is used and may be used in some of our emails to let us know which emails and links have been opened by recipients. This allows us to gauge the effectiveness of our customer communications and marketing campaigns.
We use a third party to gather information about how you and others use our Web site. For example, we will know how many users access a specific page and which links they clicked on. We use this aggregated information to understand and optimize how our site is used.
Links to Other Web Sites
Our Site includes links to other Web sites whose privacy practices may differ from those of Metropolitan Pipe. If you submit personal information to any of those sites, your information is governed by their privacy statements. We encourage you to carefully read the privacy statement of any Web site you visit.
Security
The security of your personal information is important to us. We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. If you have any questions about security on our Web site, you can contact us at info@metpipe.com.
We provide two means for you to make a purchase on our site. You can either use our order form or a third party payment option. If you use our shopping cart, the transmission of sensitive information collected on our order form is encrypted using secure socket layer technology (SSL). If you choose to use a third party payment option to pay for your order, its privacy statement and security practices will apply to your information. We encourage you to read that privacy statement before providing your information.
Additional Policy Information
Our Web site includes Widgets, which are interactive mini-programs that run on our site to provide specific services from another company (e.g. displaying the news, opinions, music, etc). Personal information, such as your email address, may be collected through the Widget. Cookies may also be set by the Widget to enable it to function properly. Information collected by this Widget is governed by the privacy policy of the company that created it.
Our Web site offers publicly accessible blogs or community forums. You should be aware that any information you provide in these areas may be read, collected, and used by others who access them.
Correcting and Updating Your Personal Information
You may edit your personal information (including shipping/billing addresses, e-mail addresses, phone numbers, etc) at any time by clicking on “My Account” at the top of every page. Alternatively, you may also contact us at ecomm@metpipe.com to update this information.
Notification of Privacy Statement Changes
We may update this privacy statement to reflect changes to our information practices. If we make any material changes we will notify you by email (sent to the e-mail address specified in your account) or by means of a notice on this Site prior to the change becoming effective. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices.
Contact Information
You can contact us about this privacy statement by writing or email us at the address below:
Metropolitan Pipe
303 Binney Street Street
Cambridge, MA, United States 02142
E-mail: ecomm@metpipe.com
MetPipe.com Privacy Policy
30 INNER BELT RD, SOMERVILLE, MA 02143  • Toll-free Phone: 1.800.METPIPE (Local: 1.617.492.6400)  • Fax: 1.617.354.3869
© 2012 Metropolitan Pipe
Privacy |
Terms & Conditions
Products
Plumbing
Heating
Pipe & Fittings
Valves
Click for Directions ››
Metropolitan Pipe & Supply Co. is a leading independent wholesale distributor of plumbing, heating, pipe, valves, fittings, and industrial supplies throughout New England. We are proud to supply the industries top brands including: Aqua-Pure, Chicago Faucets, Delta, Kohler, Mansfield, Navien, Ruud Rheem, Sloan, Grundfos, Lochinvar, Slantfin, Tekmar, Viega, Watts, Weil-McLain, Brady, Irwin, Lenox, Liberty Pumps, Little Giant, Powers, Ridgid, Zoeller, American Valve, Apollo / Conbraco, Centerline, Cimpress, Crane, Jenkins, Nibco, Powell, United, Aquatherm, Gastite, Grinnell, Hollaender, Orion and ProPress. We are Boston's largest repair parts counter stocking American Standard, Chicago, Gerber, Halsey Taylor, Leonard, Symmons, T&S and more.
